innerchef.com 2015-08-10

# Innerchef.com | Recipe Box | Fresh Ingredients | Free Home Delivery | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We, InnerChef Pvt Ltd, are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with our Terms and any other documents referred to herein) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. Information we may collect from you.

### Personal Information

When you interact with us, we automatically receive and store certain types of information, such as the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “Retargeting”). This is statistical information used to monitor the usage of our website and for advertising purposes. This information does not include personal information.

### Cookies

As you browse InnerChef, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us: (1) To estimate our audience size and usage pattern, (2) To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customize our Site according to your individual interests, (3) To speed up your searches and (4) To recognize you when you return to our Site.

### Security

We implement a secure processing server on our site when collecting information to ensure a high level of security for your personal information entered such as bank details and credit card information.

#### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [hello@innerchef.com](mailto:hello@innerchef.com?Subject=Query%20related%20to%20privacy%20policy)

###
